deskera.com 2017-06-14

# Deskera - Privacy Policy

## General

At Deskera we respect your need for online privacy and protect any information that you may share with us, in an appropriate manner. Our practice as regards use of your information is as set forth below. As a condition to use of our services, you consent to the terms of the Deskera Privacy Policy as it may be updated from time to time.

## Children’s Online Privacy Protection

In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, Deskera does not collect Personal Information from users who are under 13 years of age. Since it is necessary to provide Personal Information for creating a Deskera Account, we do not provide our services to persons below 13 years of age.

## Demo Login

Since we understand that you may wish not to disclose your Personal Information for trying out our services, we provide you the option of Demo Login for all Deskera services. The contents created by you using the Demo Login will be accessible to all persons using the Demo Login. Hence we specifically request you not to store your personal and sensitive information, files and documents while using the Demo Login.

## Information Recorded and Used

 **Personal Information:**  
During the Registration Process for creating a Deskera Account, we request for your name and email address. You will also be asked to choose a unique username and a password, which will be used solely for the purpose of providing access to your Deskera Account. Your name and email address will be used to inform you regarding new services, releases, upcoming events and changes in this privacy policy.

 **Account Usage Details:**  
Your Account Usage Details such as time, frequency, duration and pattern of use, features used and the amount of storage used will be recorded by us in order to enhance your experience of the services and to help us provide you the best possible service.

 **Contents of your Account:**  
We store and maintain files, documents, to-do lists, emails and other data stored in your Account at our facilities in the United States or any other country. Unless specified by you and agreed to by Deskera Sales Team, use of this terms of service signifies your consent to such transfer of your data outside of your country. In order to prevent loss of data due to errors or system failures, we also keep backup copies of data including the contents of your Account. Hence, your files and data may remain on our servers even after deletion or termination of your Account. We assure you that the contents of your Account will not be disclosed to anyone and will not be accessible to employees of Deskera. Neither do we process the contents of your Account for serving targeted advertisements.

 **Financial Information:**  
In case of services requiring payment, we request credit card or other payment Account information, which will be used solely for processing payments. Your Financial Information will not be stored by us. Subject to your prior consent and where necessary for processing future payments, your Financial Information will be stored in encrypted form on secure servers of reputed Payment Gateway Service Provider.

 **Visitor Details:**  
We use the Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, files accessed, errors generated, time zone, operating system and other visitor details collected in our log files to analyze the trends, administer the websites, track visitor’s movements and to improve our website.

## Cookies

We use temporary and permanent cookies to enhance your experience of our services. Temporary cookies will be removed from your computer each time you close your browser. By selecting ‘keep me signed-in’ option in Deskera services, a permanent cookie will be stored in your computer and you will not be required to sign-in by providing complete login information each time you return to our website. If you have turned cookies off, you may not be able to use registered areas of the websites.

## Links from our website

Some pages of our websites contain external links. You are advised to verify the privacy practices of such other websites. We are not responsible for the manner of use or misuse of information made available by you at such other websites. We encourage you not to provide personal Information, without assuring yourselves of the privacy policy of other websites.

## With whom we share Information

We will obtain your prior specific consent before we share or disclose your personally identifiable information to any person outside Deskera. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any Personal Information regarding visitors and users with our business partners and advertisers. Please be aware that as an Internet Service Provider, laws in various jurisdictions in which we operate may obligate us to disclose user information and the contents of the accounts to the local law enforcement authorities under specifically defined circumstances.

## How secure is your Information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored in your account. Access to your name and email address is restricted to our employees who need to know such information in connection with our services and are bound by confidentiality obligations.

## Restriction of Use

In addition to all other terms and conditions of this Agreement, you shall not: (i) transfer or otherwise make available to any third party the Services; (ii) provide any service based on the Services without prior written permission; (iii) use the third party links to sites without agreeing to their website terms and conditions; (iv) post links to third party sites or use their logo, company name, etc. without their prior written permission; or (v) use the Services for spamming and other illegal purposes.

## Your Choice in Information Use

You will be required to register for our services by providing personal information. If you choose not to provide your personal information, we will be unable to provide you the services. We do provide you with the option of not choosing a secret question and the answer to it; however, we may not be able to reset your password for you. We also provide you with the option of opting out from receiving mails from us; however, you will not be able to receive email notifications of new services, releases, upcoming events and changes to the Deskera Privacy Policy. In the event we decide to use your personal information for any purpose other than as stated in this Privacy Policy, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of your Personal Information for those other purposes.

## Accessing, Updating and Removing Personal Information

We provide users with access to their personally identifiable information. Users may correct, update or remove any such personally identifiable information either through their Deskera Account or by contacting Deskera Customer Support Services. Such changes may take up to 48 hours to take effect.

## Enforcement of Privacy Policy

We make every effort including periodic reviews to ensure that personal information provided by you is used in conformity with this privacy policy. If you have any concerns regarding our adherence to this policy or the manner in which personal information is used for the purpose of providing the services, kindly contact Deskera Customer Support Services at [support@deskera.com](mailto:s%75%70%70%6fr%74@%64esk%65ra%2ecom). This e-mail address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it . We will contact you to address your concerns and we will also co-operate with regulatory authorities in this regard if needed.

## Notification of Changes

Any changes to the Deskera Privacy Policy will be posted on our websites in order to keep you informed of any changes in nature of information collected, manner of collection, use and sharing of information. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by email and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses unless you have opted out from receiving email notifications from us. You will not receive email notification of minor changes to the Deskera Privacy Policy. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at [http://www.deskera.com/privacy-policy](https://www.deskera.com/privacy-policy) periodically.

## End of Privacy Policy

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at [legal@deskera.com](mailto:%6cegal@%64es%6ber%61%2e%63om)
